<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Writer / Blogger</title>
    <link>../../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262</link>
    <description>Anyone here fancy themselves as the next Wordsworth or just simply like to blog now and again? We&#39;re after some talented writers to join the Bitbay team, yes that&#39;s right we are expanding AGAIN!

Ideally you&#39;d have solid crypto/blockchain knowledge and will already be familiar with Bitbay.market.

We are looking for someone who can grasp technical concepts as well as write in layman&#39;s terms to a wider audience.

Knowledge of SEO would be advantageous but isn&#39;t mandatory.

Hours are flexible so you can treat this as extra income to supplement your current day job if you&#39;d wish. This opportunity will suit someone who is happy to communicate with our team on Slack and report back on work done regularly. This is a remote working position from your own home/office. 

If interested, please get in touch with a covernote explaining why you think you&#39;re a good fit fo the role, your current knowledge of Bitbay and of crypto projects in general and your CV. aletha@bitbay.market</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 15:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
    <atom:link href="../../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Writer / Blogger</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="../../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Anyone here fancy themselves as the next Wordsworth or just simply like to blog now and again? We’re after some talented writers to join the Bitbay team, yes that’s right we are expanding AGAIN!</p>
<p>Ideally you’d have solid crypto/blockchain knowledge and will already be familiar with Bitbay.market.</p>
<p>We are looking for someone who can grasp technical concepts as well as write in layman’s terms to a wider audience.</p>
<p>Knowledge of SEO would be advantageous but isn’t mandatory.</p>
<p>Hours are flexible so you can treat this as extra income to supplement your current day job if you’d wish. This opportunity will suit someone who is happy to communicate with our team on Slack and report back on work done regularly. This is a remote working position from your own home/office.</p>
<p>If interested, please get in touch with a covernote explaining why you think you’re a good fit fo the role, your current knowledge of Bitbay and of crypto projects in general and your CV. aletha@bitbay.market</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="../../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>../../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 15:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-post-1262-1</guid>
        <source url="../../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262.rss">Writer / Blogger</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
