<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</title>
    <link>../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68</link>
    <description>
**Graphics Designer -remote/home** - Am Pleased to Announce this position has now been filled. 
 
Want to learn about Blockchain, crytocurrency/digital currencies/Alt-coins similar to Bitcoin, ethereum but can&#39;t get a foot in due to lack of experience? Then this may be the perfect opportunity if you can spare some free time working on live projects in return for hands-on learning around your schedule?
  
Adobe illustrator / Photoshop / Indesign
  
This role can be undertaken remotely so it doesn&#39;t matter where in the world you are based! As long as you have transferable graphics skills and a good internet connection please feel free to apply!
  
Bitbay have been around for several years and have one of the world&#39;s top developers working on our software. We have a very active, friendly slack community where you will bounce off the core team as well as investors.
  
We are happy to have more than one designer take on these tasks depending on your workload. The tasks are relatively simple and a great way to introduce yourself to the world of blockchain technology.
  
Build 20-30 graphics at the relevant size for social media use – Twitter, Facebook etc. They will provide a spreadsheet with the content and the graphic assets.
  
You must be passionate about learning new things and have an interest in their project and what they do. You might find this to be easy as the software itself is quite revolutionary. 
  
You will have to file reports on your progress and work in a fast and concise manner. You will also be able to learn a lot about the field and some of the secrets of the trade from one of the top cryptocurrency developers. 

You will also be able to take part in a very large collaborative team effort and this will help you hone in on your skills and of course, you will end up with an excellent portfolio of work to reference on your CV and make yourself more employable for future work in the blockchain space from larger firms.
  
Experience in one of the following platforms would be ideal:
 
• Adobe illustrator
• Photoshop

please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 20:49:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
    <atom:link href="../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@Wout78 Wouter]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="../../../forum-archive/u/wout78">@Wout78</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p>Hello my name is Wouter and I have sent you a message about graphic design, but I’m not really sure I have sent it correctly. Could you please let me know if you received my message?</p>
<p>Kind regards,<br>
Wouter</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68/2</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 21:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-post-68-2</guid>
        <source url="../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68.rss">Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
          <p><a href="../../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
          <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Graphics Designer -remote/home</strong> - Am Pleased to Announce this position has now been filled.</p>
<p>Want to learn about Blockchain, crytocurrency/digital currencies/Alt-coins similar to Bitcoin, ethereum but can’t get a foot in due to lack of experience? Then this may be the perfect opportunity if you can spare some free time working on live projects in return for hands-on learning around your schedule?</p>
<p>Adobe illustrator / Photoshop / Indesign</p>
<p>This role can be undertaken remotely so it doesn’t matter where in the world you are based! As long as you have transferable graphics skills and a good internet connection please feel free to apply!</p>
<p>Bitbay have been around for several years and have one of the world’s top developers working on our software. We have a very active, friendly slack community where you will bounce off the core team as well as investors.</p>
<p>We are happy to have more than one designer take on these tasks depending on your workload. The tasks are relatively simple and a great way to introduce yourself to the world of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Build 20-30 graphics at the relevant size for social media use – Twitter, Facebook etc. They will provide a spreadsheet with the content and the graphic assets.</p>
<p>You must be passionate about learning new things and have an interest in their project and what they do. You might find this to be easy as the software itself is quite revolutionary.</p>
<p>You will have to file reports on your progress and work in a fast and concise manner. You will also be able to learn a lot about the field and some of the secrets of the trade from one of the top cryptocurrency developers.</p>
<p>You will also be able to take part in a very large collaborative team effort and this will help you hone in on your skills and of course, you will end up with an excellent portfolio of work to reference on your CV and make yourself more employable for future work in the blockchain space from larger firms.</p>
<p>Experience in one of the following platforms would be ideal:</p>
<p>• Adobe illustrator<br>
• Photoshop</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
          </blockquote>
          <p><a href="../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-post-68-1</guid>
        <source url="../../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68.rss">Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
