<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:discourse="http://www.discourse.org/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Recruitment and Bounty - BitBay Community</title>
    <link>../../forum-archive/c/recruitment-and-bounty</link>
    <description>Topics in the &#39;Recruitment and Bounty&#39; category Can’t get enough Bitbay? Then consider working for us and earning some! Find out here what full time or part time jobs are available; as well as what bounties are on offer more ad-hoc work. Hours are flexible if part time so you can work remotely in your free time and bag yourself some $bay!</description>
    
      <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 15:02:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <atom:link href="../../forum-archive/c/recruitment-and-bounty.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
          <title>Writer / Blogger</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Anyone here fancy themselves as the next Wordsworth or just simply like to blog now and again? We’re after some talented writers to join the Bitbay team, yes that’s right we are expanding AGAIN!</p>
<p>Ideally you’d have solid crypto/blockchain knowledge and will already be familiar with Bitbay.market.</p>
<p>We are looking for someone who can grasp technical concepts as well as write in layman’s terms to a wider audience.</p>
<p>Knowledge of SEO would be advantageous but isn’t mandatory.</p>
<p>Hours are flexible so you can treat this as extra income to supplement your current day job if you’d wish. This opportunity will suit someone who is happy to communicate with our team on Slack and report back on work done regularly. This is a remote working position from your own home/office.</p>
<p>If interested, please get in touch with a covernote explaining why you think you’re a good fit fo the role, your current knowledge of Bitbay and of crypto projects in general and your CV. aletha@bitbay.market</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 09 Apr 2018 15:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-1262</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/writer-blogger/1262.rss">Writer / Blogger</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Lead Full Stack Javascript Developer – permanent or contract. – Remote work</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Lead Full Stack Javascript Developer – permanent or contract. – Remote work</p>
<p>Bitbay is actively looking to add to its already established development team by adding a Senior / Lead node.js dev Full stack developer to join an existing team in the development of mobile apps.</p>
<p>The successful developer /Analyst Programmer/Software Engineer help build out the business application and APIs and will be:</p>
<p>Well versed in front and backend JavaScript development</p>
<p>experienced in structuring code<br>
experienced managing developers<br>
angularjs/reactjs/nodejs/tests<br>
optimisation in mind<br>
please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 3</p>
            <p>Participants: 3</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/lead-full-stack-javascript-developer-permanent-or-contract-remote-work/1216">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/lead-full-stack-javascript-developer-permanent-or-contract-remote-work/1216</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 10:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-1216</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/lead-full-stack-javascript-developer-permanent-or-contract-remote-work/1216.rss">Lead Full Stack Javascript Developer – permanent or contract. – Remote work</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>**Foreign Community Manager - Chinese **</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>**Foreign Community Manager - Chinese **</p>
<p>Bitbay are looking for language speakers to establish, grow and maintain our Foreign Communities. At present, we are looking for a Chinese language speaker who also has a strong grasp of English to undertake accurate translation work. We envisage we need someone who can spare approx 20 hours a week.</p>
<p>All foreign community managers are expected to build a community in our own forum + minimum 1 social media.<br>
Translation and posting of weekly and monthly newsletter + any other announcements are mandatory<br>
Translating our site<br>
Making subtitles for our tutorials<br>
Improving the translation in our wallet<br>
Community managers are rewarded with $Bay for each member that joins the community up till 2000 members. After 2000 members are reached community manager is rewarded a maintenance reward of $bay a month.<br>
The reward will be adjusted in accordance to price change for Bay</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/foreign-community-manager-chinese/1215">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/foreign-community-manager-chinese/1215</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 10:17:54 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-1215</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/foreign-community-manager-chinese/1215.rss">**Foreign Community Manager - Chinese **</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Animator / Motion Graphics Designer</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Hello everyone! We are looking to hire a talented animator to work with our art directors in creating explainer /intro videos to a voice over (we already have). remote work, flexible hours available. must be an experienced animator/motion graphics designer able to coordinate work in slack. Please email your CV and portfolio to aletha@bitbay.market</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/animator-motion-graphics-designer/1161">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/animator-motion-graphics-designer/1161</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 11:46:27 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-1161</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/animator-motion-graphics-designer/1161.rss">Animator / Motion Graphics Designer</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Senior SEO Specialist / Manager **POSITION FILLED**</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Senior SEO Specialist / Manager</strong> - ideally full time but can consider part time too</p>
<p>Bitbay is looking for an experienced Specialist / Manager to join our Social Media and Web team.</p>
<p>The approach is to lead with insight driven strategies brought to life by content/experience opportunities and strong technical backbone. Although client websites/apps and digital experiences are the key focus areas, this role is also encouraged to provide strategies and recommendations that demonstrate a deep understanding of Bitbay’s overall offerings. You will own the definition and execution of search strategies including performance tracking, continual optimization and improvement.</p>
<p>Responsibilities:<br>
•	Own the development and execution of search driven strategies<br>
•	While focusing primarily on searcher behaviour, also leverage a wide range of additional research sources to find key insights and then communicate them effectively to the wider teams<br>
•	Demonstrate knowledge and utilization of advanced productivity and automation concepts to reduce time spent gathering data while maximizing development of insights and strategies<br>
•	Define search driven guidelines around page content, mobile friendliness, site architecture, URL structure, page titles, meta descriptions, headings, schema markup, page speed, anchor text, internal linking, site maps, etc.<br>
•	Create content strategies in collaboration with the working team that leverage professional and user generated content to maximize return<br>
•	Combine paid search and organic search data when available to reduce costs while maximizing key business activities<br>
•	Ability to review existing site content, structure and technology and provide optimization recommendations.<br>
•	Define search requirements and provide direction to copywriters, designers and engineers while quality checking implementation.<br>
•	Develop a framework and reports to systematically track and improve search performance<br>
•	Stay up-to-date with changes in how search engines measure authority<br>
•	Advise on website development tweaks to manage migrations while maximizing search visibility: for example, redirects, error pages, use of JavaScript/AJAX<br>
•	Content development best practices.<br>
Requirements:<br>
•	Solid SEO experience– ideally with multiple websites.<br>
•	Demonstrated achievements in systematically improving search rankings that translated into traffic growth and improved site conversion.<br>
•	Deep understanding of website personalization, automation and the search impacts of each and how to mitigate<br>
•	Strong knowledge of the cryptosphere/blockchain related projects.<br>
•	Strong communication skills, both written and verbal<br>
•	In depth knowledge of user experience concepts<br>
•	Strong technical understanding as it relates to early SEO in the web development process, and the ability to work in partnership with a development team.<br>
•	Very strong analytical skills with a demonstrated ability to leverage multiple data sources to inform decision-making.<br>
•	Systematic approach to identifying opportunities/issues, defining solutions and executing action plans.<br>
•	Great attention to detail combined with the ability to prioritize and meet aggressive targets and deadlines.<br>
•	Passion for staying current in a rapidly evolving environment and leveraging tools and online forums to gain a competitive edge.<br>
•	Be able to adapt to changing consumer behavior and emerging trends changing on a daily basis.</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/senior-seo-specialist-manager-position-filled/75">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/senior-seo-specialist-manager-position-filled/75</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 10:20:54 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-75</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/senior-seo-specialist-manager-position-filled/75.rss">Senior SEO Specialist / Manager **POSITION FILLED**</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Market Research Analyst</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Market Research Analyst</strong> – exciting opportunity to work across a diverse platform / user base and carve out “market research techniques” in the cryptosphere!</p>
<p>Full or part time REMOTE work.</p>
<p>Bitbay is looking to hire someone who loves conducting market research and user surveys!<br>
Ideally this will be creative analysis of qualitative eCommerce consumer and Crypto investor research strategies.<br>
The successful candidate will work closely with the Marketing Manager and Social Media Team.<br>
Bitbay offers a very diverse range of “use cases” from buying/selling to transferring Fiat to Crypto to setting up a trust fund to conducting contract/employment services<br>
The use cases need in depth analysis to maximise the adoption and benefit to our investors and users.<br>
The position of Market Research Analyst will be highly varied  and highly autonomous giving you scope to design your own research methods, surveys, polls, in a wide range of mediums – using social media such as twitter, facebook as well as communities such as slack groups, face to face seminars etc.<br>
Ideally we are looking for someone to have an established track record in designing, carrying out and managing social research. Management of complex research projects which involve a range of people, cultures, communities, buyers/sellers, businesses and disciplines. Strong analytical background, with experience of survey design, delivery and analysis. Strong communication skills and experience of collaborative working. Development of clear, pragmatic and manageable delivery plans using project management skills. Be self-motivated and comfortable working at pace.</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/market-research-analyst/74">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/market-research-analyst/74</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 10:08:32 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-74</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/market-research-analyst/74.rss">Market Research Analyst</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Sellers to sell items on our marketplace</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>eCommerce sellers  such as eBay or Amazon to list and sell a variety of items on our marketplace</p>
<p>NO SELLER FEES!<br>
NO LISTING FEES!<br>
NO MONTHLY FEES!<br>
NO INSERTION FEES!<br>
ABILITY TO ACCEPT FIAT OR CRYPTO FOR PAYMENT?<br>
KEEP 100% PROFIT?!</p>
<pre><code>       Why wouldn't you want to sell your items on our marketplace?!
</code></pre>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 4</p>
            <p>Participants: 3</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/sellers-to-sell-items-on-our-marketplace/73">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/sellers-to-sell-items-on-our-marketplace/73</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-73</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/sellers-to-sell-items-on-our-marketplace/73.rss">Sellers to sell items on our marketplace</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Lead Full Stack Javascript Developer - **POSITION FILLED**</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Lead Full Stack Javascript Developer – permanent or contract. – Remote work</strong></p>
<p>Bitbay  is actively looking to add to its already established development team by adding a Senior / Lead node.js dev Full stack developer to join an existing team in the development of mobile apps.</p>
<p>The successful developer /Analyst Programmer/Software Engineer help build out the business application and APIs and will be:</p>
<p>Well versed in front and backend JavaScript development</p>
<ul>
<li>experienced in structuring code</li>
<li>experienced managing developers</li>
<li>angularjs/reactjs/nodejs/tests</li>
<li>optimisation in mind</li>
</ul>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/lead-full-stack-javascript-developer-position-filled/72">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/lead-full-stack-javascript-developer-position-filled/72</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:50:08 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-72</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/lead-full-stack-javascript-developer-position-filled/72.rss">Lead Full Stack Javascript Developer - **POSITION FILLED**</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Foreign Community Manager(s) - Korean, Greek, Japanese, German, Portuguese</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>**Foreign Community Manager(s) - Korean (x2) Greek, Japanese, German, Portuguese **</p>
<p>Bitbay are looking for  language speakers to establish, grow and maintain our Foreign Communities:<br>
Korean, Greek, Japanese, German, Portuguese<br>
All foreign community managers are expected to build a community in our own forum + minimum 1 social media.<br>
Translation and posting of weekly and monthly newsletter + any other announcements are mandatory<br>
Translating our site<br>
Making subtitles for our tutorials<br>
Improving the translation in our wallet<br>
Community managers are rewarded with $Bay for each member that joins the community up till 2000 members. After 2000 members are reached community manager is rewarded a maintenance reward of $bay a month.<br>
The reward will be adjusted in accordance to price change for Bay</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 23</p>
            <p>Participants: 13</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/foreign-community-manager-s-korean-greek-japanese-german-portuguese/71">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/foreign-community-manager-s-korean-greek-japanese-german-portuguese/71</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:45:24 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-71</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/foreign-community-manager-s-korean-greek-japanese-german-portuguese/71.rss">Foreign Community Manager(s) - Korean, Greek, Japanese, German, Portuguese</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Marketing Manager / Head of Marketing</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Marketing Manager / Head of Marketing REMOTE WORK around your day job! £negotiable</strong></p>
<p>Do you have an interest in blockchain, bitcoin, Ethereum related projects, alt-coin, cryptocurrencies and are looking for remote work around your day job? If the Answer is yes, then my client would love to hear from you! Pay is negotiable</p>
<p>We are looking for a Head of Marketing with an interest in Blockchain technology to lead, motivate and manage a team of marketing and communications professionals in the testing, creation, management, delivery and review of key marketing campaigns within agreed strategies, plans and budgets.</p>
<ul>
<li>To help lead on the development of integrated strategies and plans, ensuring that the team capitalize on every opportunity to build brand, raise awareness, deepen understanding, drive action and grow awareness/user interaction with the software and currency.</li>
</ul>
<p>Coordinating with the Art Director and IT Development team, you will help lead the brand creative development to lead the rebrand and continued development of the brand throughout the transformation programme and all the marketing activity.</p>
<p>You will need to develop strategies to target investors and users of a blockchain / cryptocurrency software platform. Both are very unique target markets so the Head of Marketing will need to devise strategies in collaboration with  other internal teams such as Web development/SEO/Social Media on how to gather market data for analysis and from this, create and devise specific plans.</p>
<p>You will ideally have an interest in blockchain, bitcoin, Ethereum related projects, alt-coin, cryptocurrencies and will be comfortable adding structure to unstructured teams.</p>
<p>The team are global and are all remote  workers so this role will involve heavy use of tools such as slack, gsuite, Asana, Skype for regular communication with the team.<br>
Other responsibilities will include:</p>
<p>•	Working on low budget projects - Manage and control budget and review performance<br>
•	Lead media agency selection for PR<br>
•	Develop marketing activity with the commercial team including promotional plans and launches</p>
<p>You will need:</p>
<p>•	To be a marketing professional with strong brand and advertising leadership experience Ideally with a mixture of B2B, B2C or C2C experience.<br>
•	The ability to translate customer insight into clear and compelling customer messages and communication<br>
•	The ability to join up multiple strands of activity to land in the market at the same time for maximum impact in terms of impact, influence, and ultimately sales<br>
•	To be highly commercially aware<br>
•	Excellent understanding of all elements of the marketing mix and the role of brand, advertising, and visual communications within this<br>
•	Strong commercial and numerical analytical skills</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/marketing-manager-head-of-marketing/70">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/marketing-manager-head-of-marketing/70</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-70</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/marketing-manager-head-of-marketing/70.rss">Marketing Manager / Head of Marketing</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Full Stack Python developer OR Front end PYQT GUI</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>I am pleased to announce this position has been filled!</strong></p>
<p><strong>Full Stack Python developer OR Front end PYQT GUI</strong></p>
<p>REMOTE WORK in your spare time from your HOME – pay is negotiable</p>
<p>This role can be undertaken remotely so it doesn’t matter where in the world you are based. As long as you have transferable technical skills and a good internet connection please feel free to apply.</p>
<p>Front End developer / UI (User Interface) Python/PyQt or C++ Developer / Programmer / Software Engineer with interest in cryptography and peer to peer networks</p>
<p>We are interested in finding and training a few cryptocurrency developers or people who want to be more familiar with the field. Bitbay has been established for several years and has one of the world’s top developers working on our software.</p>
<p>We are the first company to offer decentralized peer to peer serverless markets and unbreakable contracts in a full-fledged contracting platform.</p>
<p>•	The tasks would vary but would include redevelopment/ re-skinning our desktop application.</p>
<p>It would be helpful if you have a background in peer to peer networking, cryptography, network programming or security. It would be nice if you were familiar with design and UI/UX development.<br>
Working remotely, you will have to file reports on your progress and work in a fast and concise manner. You will also be able to learn a lot about the field and some of the secrets of the trade from one of the top cryptocurrency developers.</p>
<p>You will also be able to take part in a very large collaborative team effort and this will help you hone in on your skills.</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 4</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/full-stack-python-developer-or-front-end-pyqt-gui/69">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/full-stack-python-developer-or-front-end-pyqt-gui/69</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:36:49 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>Yes</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-69</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/full-stack-python-developer-or-front-end-pyqt-gui/69.rss">Full Stack Python developer OR Front end PYQT GUI</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Graphics Designer -remote/home</strong> - Am Pleased to Announce this position has now been filled.</p>
<p>Want to learn about Blockchain, crytocurrency/digital currencies/Alt-coins similar to Bitcoin, ethereum but can’t get a foot in due to lack of experience? Then this may be the perfect opportunity if you can spare some free time working on live projects in return for hands-on learning around your schedule?</p>
<p>Adobe illustrator / Photoshop / Indesign</p>
<p>This role can be undertaken remotely so it doesn’t matter where in the world you are based! As long as you have transferable graphics skills and a good internet connection please feel free to apply!</p>
<p>Bitbay have been around for several years and have one of the world’s top developers working on our software. We have a very active, friendly slack community where you will bounce off the core team as well as investors.</p>
<p>We are happy to have more than one designer take on these tasks depending on your workload. The tasks are relatively simple and a great way to introduce yourself to the world of blockchain technology.</p>
<p>Build 20-30 graphics at the relevant size for social media use – Twitter, Facebook etc. They will provide a spreadsheet with the content and the graphic assets.</p>
<p>You must be passionate about learning new things and have an interest in their project and what they do. You might find this to be easy as the software itself is quite revolutionary.</p>
<p>You will have to file reports on your progress and work in a fast and concise manner. You will also be able to learn a lot about the field and some of the secrets of the trade from one of the top cryptocurrency developers.</p>
<p>You will also be able to take part in a very large collaborative team effort and this will help you hone in on your skills and of course, you will end up with an excellent portfolio of work to reference on your CV and make yourself more employable for future work in the blockchain space from larger firms.</p>
<p>Experience in one of the following platforms would be ideal:</p>
<p>• Adobe illustrator<br>
• Photoshop</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 2</p>
            <p>Participants: 2</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-68</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/graphics-designer-position-now-filled/68.rss">Graphics Designer - POSITION NOW FILLED</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Social Media Manager **POSITION FILLED**</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Social Media Manager</strong></p>
<p>To Manage the Social Media Team and lead the development and use of an automated Social Media Engine.</p>
<ul>
<li>develop a social media strategy and set goals to increase brand awareness and increase engagement</li>
<li>manage all social media channels such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Google + and Instagram</li>
<li>plan content and delivery and use tools like Buffer and Asana to manage multiple social media channels</li>
<li>develop and manage competitions and campaigns that promote our organisation and brand</li>
<li>plan engaging blog posts and articles</li>
<li>create engaging multimedia content such as videos, and/or outsource this effectively</li>
<li>form key relationships with influencers across the social media platforms</li>
<li>manage and facilitate social media communities by responding to social media posts and developing discussions</li>
<li>monitor and report on performance on social media platforms using tools such as Google Analytics</li>
<li>manage junior staff such as a social media executive or assistant</li>
<li>educate other staff on the use of social media and promote its use within your company (in-house roles)</li>
</ul>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/social-media-manager-position-filled/67">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/social-media-manager-position-filled/67</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-67</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/social-media-manager-position-filled/67.rss">Social Media Manager **POSITION FILLED**</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>Social Media Analyst **POSITION FILLED**</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p><strong>Social Media Analyst – part time – REMOTE WORK FROM HOME!</strong></p>
<p>Do you love social media? Have new and exciting ideas to boost a company’s engagement and improve their channels? Love creating content and engaging with followers?</p>
<p>Do you also have an interest in blockchain, bitcoin, Ethereum related projects, alt-coin, cryptocurrencies? If so, then please read on!</p>
<p>Bitbay is looking for a highly creative and energetic individual who is addicted to social media and has experience in managing social media accounts, to join the global team. You’ll be on the frontline of our content strategies, creating and posting content on all of the social media platforms. You’ll have a strong understanding of current trends in the social media sphere with a very strong sense of aesthetics and style.<br>
This role provides tremendous opportunities for the right candidate: to capture the energy and rapid pace of a fast growing cryptocurrency provider while being responsible for a sizeable and growing part of their global footprint.<br>
Responsibilities</p>
<p>•	Develop social media strategies by planning, researching and creating highly engaging content that targets global audiences across various social media channels (e.g., Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, YouTube)<br>
•	Conceptualise and execute innovative social media campaigns and competitions to drive awareness and engagement<br>
•	Track and monitor daily account activities (including growth, engagement etc.) and performance of campaigns<br>
•	Monitor and listen to online conversation within company’s social media channels; respond to questions of followers and make strategic suggestions based on this conversation<br>
•	Conceive and develop efficient and intuitive marketing campaigns with influencers/brand ambassadors to gain maximum exposure for the brand via various online platforms<br>
•	Work within a variety of social media management tools and content management system for scheduling and publish content on a global scale<br>
•	Work with our design team to create unique and engaging content<br>
Required Skills/Knowledge/Experience:</p>
<p>•	  Must have an excellent eye for great pictures and a strong sense of aesthetics<br>
•	  Enthusiastic content creator on social media<br>
•	  Active profiles on a minimum of two social media channels<br>
•	  Ability to commit to the role for at least three months, preferably six with the option to extend<br>
•	  Excellent writing and communications skills<br>
•	  Positive attitude, willingness to go the extra mile<br>
•	  Having your own blog and WordPress knowledge will be a plus<br>
•	  Photoshop experience also a bonus!<br>
In return you will get:</p>
<p>•	Bonuses paid in cryptocurrency<br>
•	Invaluable insight into the world of a highly innovative blockchain company<br>
•	Excellent experience coordinating with global teams, heads of departments and creative divisions.</p>
<p>please email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/social-media-analyst-position-filled/66">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/social-media-analyst-position-filled/66</link>
          <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 09:30:30 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>No</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-66</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/social-media-analyst-position-filled/66.rss">Social Media Analyst **POSITION FILLED**</source>
        </item>
        <item>
          <title>About the Recruitment and Bounty category</title>
          <dc:creator><![CDATA[@aletha]]></dc:creator>
          <category>Recruitment and Bounty</category>
          <description><![CDATA[
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/u/aletha">@aletha</a> wrote:</p>
            <blockquote>
              <p>Can’t get enough Bitbay? Then consider working for us and earning some! Find out here what full time or part time jobs are available; as well as what bounties are on offer more ad-hoc work. Hours are flexible if part time so you can work remotely in your free time and bag yourself some $bay!</p>
<p><strong>Please ensure you include a covernote and your CV/Linkedin page showing areas of relevance to the positions you are applying for.</strong></p>
<p>For details positions available please comment against them or email your CV to aletha@bitbay.market our Recruitment Manager.</p>
            </blockquote>
            <p>Posts: 1</p>
            <p>Participants: 1</p>
            <p><a href="../../forum-archive/t/about-the-recruitment-and-bounty-category/39">Read full topic</a></p>
          ]]></description>
          <link>../../forum-archive/t/about-the-recruitment-and-bounty-category/39</link>
          <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 12:54:40 +0000</pubDate>
          <discourse:topicPinned>Yes</discourse:topicPinned>
          <discourse:topicClosed>No</discourse:topicClosed>
          <discourse:topicArchived>No</discourse:topicArchived>
          <guid isPermaLink="false">forum.bitbay.market-topic-39</guid>
          <source url="../../forum-archive/t/about-the-recruitment-and-bounty-category/39.rss">About the Recruitment and Bounty category</source>
        </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
